[
  [
    {
      "question": "What is Tame Impala‚Äôs real name?",
      "answers": ["Matt Flynn", "Kevin Parker", "Ryan Lewis", "Tom Impale"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What nuts are used to make marzipan?",
      "answers": ["Marzinuts", "Hazelnuts", "Almonds", "Deez"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the current Prime Minister of England?",
      "answers": [
        "Boris Johnson",
        "David Cameron",
        "Prince William",
        "Simon Cowell"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many times has Trump been married?",
      "answers": ["2", "3", "4", "5"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the GOAT of hotdog eating?",
      "answers": [
        "Nathan Fielder",
        "Joey Chestnut",
        "Matt Stonie",
        "Your mother"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a current NBA player",
      "answers": [
        "Ha Ha Clinton-Dix",
        "Shabazz Napier",
        "General Booty",
        "Budda Baker"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In Genesis the first book of the Old Testament, who does God first tell to get circumcised",
      "answers": ["Moses", "Abraham", "Joseph", "Om Naphade"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What class did I fail my freshman year?",
      "answers": ["MATH 520", "MATH 540", "CSCI 0180", "CSCI 0190"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Which Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtle wears a purple mask?",
      "answers": ["Leonardo", "Raphael", "Donatello", "Michelangelo"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which artist painted the Sistine Chapel?",
      "answers": ["Leonardo", "Raphael", "Donatello", "Michelangelo"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the molecular formula for ammonia, the active ingredient in smelling salts?",
      "answers": ["CO3", "NH3", "NH4+", "C17H21NO4"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What color are intermediate tires in f1?",
      "answers": ["Red", "Blue", "Green", "Magenta"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following US presidents was not assassinated?",
      "answers": [
        "Chester A. Arthur",
        "James A. Garfield",
        "William McKinley",
        "John F. Kennedy"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Recently the Boston Red Sox gave up the most runs in a game this season, how many was it?",
      "answers": ["17", "21", "24", "28"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How old was Chief Keef when he dropped cult classic Love Sosa?",
      "answers": ["14", "16", "18", "19"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Chionophobia is the fear of what?",
      "answers": ["Chinese people", "Hospitals", "Doors", "Snow"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "What does CBT stand for?",
      "answers": [
        "Clock and Bell Tower",
        "Cognitive Behavior Therapy",
        "Conditional Bivariate Theorem",
        "Cock and Ball Torture"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of these albums released in 2022 has the longest tracklist?",
      "answers": [
        "Mr. Morale & the Big Steppers - Kendrick Lamar",
        "Fun Wav Bounces Vol 2 - Calvin Harris",
        "Laurel Hell - Mitski",
        "2000 - Joey Bada$$"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the word for S in the NATO phonetic alphabet",
      "answers": ["Sugma", "Sierra", "Sugandese", "Samuel"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which color scheme do printers commonly use?",
      "answers": ["RGB", "CMYK", "HSV", "SMD"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which album won the 2022 Grammy for Album of the Year?",
      "answers": [
        "Donda - Kanye West",
        "An Evening with Silk Sonic - Silk Sonic",
        "Sour - Wifey üòç",
        "We Are - Jon Batiste"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "In J. Cole's 2014 hit song No Role Modelz, the Interlude is a quote from who?",
      "answers": [
        "Sleepy Joe",
        "John F. Kennedy",
        "George W. Bush",
        "Some random southern guy"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is a the title of real Yeat song?",
      "answers": ["F√ºck M√´", "Stizzy Talk", "Big Ston√´z", "Tonk Donka"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "How many times have I shit on grass?",
      "answers": ["0 b/c I'm a grown person", "1", "2", "3+"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "Who is the most decorated Olympian?",
      "answers": [
        "Michael Phelps",
        "Simone Biles",
        "Takashi Ono",
        "Usain Bolt"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Who is the face of the US hundred dollar bill?",
      "answers": [
        "George Washington",
        "Abraham Lincoln",
        "Ulysses S. Grant",
        "Benjamin Franklin"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "What is Tyler the Creators real name?",
      "answers": ["Rakim", "Darold", "Bennett", "Tyler"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "How many times was Donald Trump impeached?",
      "answers": ["0", "1", "2", "I want to be in his peach"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "Where are the Hanging Gardens located?",
      "answers": ["Austria", "Iraq", "Hungary", "Morocco"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How long is the Ninety Mile Beach",
      "answers": ["55 miles", "90 miles", "100 miles", "150 kilometers"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How much does Frank Ocean's Homer collaboration cock ring retail for?",
      "answers": ["$5k", "$10k", "$25k", "$50k"],
      "correctIndex": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "In song of the summer Cash In Cash Out, what brand of sleeveless shirt was 21 Savage wearing?",
      "answers": ["Gucci", "Fendi", "Givenchy", "Louis Vuitton"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    }
  ],
  [
    {
      "question": "What is up when Flo Milli steps up in the party?",
      "answers": ["Hands", "Dicks", "Roof", "Spirits"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "King Duncan is the King in which Shakespeare play?",
      "answers": [
        "Macbeth",
        "Hamlet",
        "The Tempest",
        "Henry the Fourth Part 3"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT one of 5 D-Day beaches",
      "answers": ["Utah Beach", "Omaha Beach", "Juno Beach", "White Beach"],
      "correctIndex": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "On his 2019 hit single, Sanguine Paradise, how tall does Lil Uzi Vert claim to be when standing on his money",
      "answers": [
        "5' 8\" (very tall btw)",
        "6' 6\"",
        "9' 6\"",
        "As tall as Shaquille O'Neale"
      ],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How many balls are on a pool table at the start of a game",
      "answers": ["15", "16", "21", "22"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is NOT a word for a basic aromatic blend in cooking?",
      "answers": ["Mirepoix", "Sofrito", "Za‚Äôatar", "Battuto"],
      "correctIndex": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "On how many separate albums has Pop Smoke released Dior? (X and X(Deluxe) do not count as separate albums)",
      "answers": ["3", "4", "5", "6"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How many guys have I pissed with at Brown?",
      "answers": ["3", "5", "7", "10"],
      "correctIndex": 1
    }
  ]
]
